可以走了吗
You ready to go?
让我先把这个弄完
Let me just finish this.
嘿  罗斯  瞧我的
Hey, Ross. Check this out.
我还不会
Yeah, I can't do that.
你在做什么呢
What are you doing?
你看过这个吗
Have you seen this?
这是我们大学校友会的新网站
It's our new alumni website for college.
你可以发布状态
You can post messages for people,
让大家知道你的近况
let everyone know what you're up to.
太好了  一个更快速方式
Oh, great. A faster way to tell people
昭告大家  我失业又没小孩
that I'm unemployed and childless.
知道大家的近况挺有意思的
It's actually interesting to find out what people are doing.
记得艾卓雅·里奇吗
Remember Andrea Rich?
不肯跟你上床的那个高个子女生吗
That tall girl that wouldn't sleep with you?
她的网络公司倒闭了
Well, her Internet company went under,
还在游艇事故里失去一只耳朵
and she lost an ear in a boating accident.
我敢说她现在一定会跟你上床了
Bet she'd sleep with you now.
不行  我已经发邮件问过她了
No, I already e-mailed her.
让我看看  你给自己写的什么
Let me see what you wrote about yourself.
古生物学博士  有两个小孩
Doctor of paleontology, two kids.
等等  你跟卡罗尔分开的原因
Wait a second. You split with Carol
是因为兴趣不同吗
because you had different interests?
我认为你跟她分开的原因
I think you split with Carol
是因为某个兴趣相同
because you had one very similar interest.
我等一下再写好了  去拿件外套
I'm gonna finish this later, okay? Let me just grab my coat.
好的
Okay!
怎样  你花了两分钟就能学会吗
What, did you think you learned how to do it in the last two minutes?
或许  我们可以帮他写完
Maybe we finish this for him.
同时  我在实验室里克隆出一只恐龙
Also, I cloned a dinosaur in my lab.
她现在是我的女朋友了
She is now my girlfriend.
我不在乎世俗的眼光
I don't care what society says,
它给了我最棒的性生活
it's the best sex I've ever had.
然后  发布
And send.
不  你怎么能这么对他
No, no-- You can't do that to him.
-好了  我们走  -老兄
- All right, let's go.  - Dude!
我想你很清楚的证明了
I think you made it clear you can't be trusted
不能让你在室内碰球
with the ball inside the house.
然后  发布
And send.
《老友记》  第九季 第17集  罗斯的"追悼会"
Friends S09E17 The One With The Memorial Service
嘿  篮球打得怎么样
Hey. How was basketball?
很好玩
It was fun.
一直玩到钱德勒的眼睛被手指戳到
Right up until Chandler got a finger in the eye.
哦  天啊  是谁弄的
Oh, no! Who did that?
钱德勒自己
Chandler. Yeah.
嘿
Hey!
-瑞秋  -怎样
- Rach?  - Yeah?
哈格吉为什么会在艾玛的婴儿车里
What's Huggsy doing in the crib with Emma?
她到处爬的时候看到了
She was just crawling around and found him,
所以我就让他们一起睡觉觉
so I just let her sleep with him.
-没关系吧  -当然  没关系
- That's all right, isn't it?  - Of course. Yeah.
只是填充玩具而已
It's a stuffed animal, you know?
是给小孩玩的  不是给大人的
It's for kids. Not for adults.
这点我知道
I know that.
乔伊  你确定吗  我知道你很爱他
Joey, you're sure? I mean, I know how much you love him.
瑞秋  我们说清楚
Rachel, let's be clear on this, okay?
我没有很爱他
I do not love Huggsy.
我只是以正常的程度喜欢他
I like him a normal amount.
好吧  但是艾玛爱死他了
All right. Well, Emma loves him.
是啊  能不爱嘛  他那么好
Yeah. Well, why wouldn't she? He's a wonderful person!
-嗨  -嘿  菲比  你还好吗
- Hi.  - Hey, Phoebe. How you doing?
-你感觉好点了吗  -分手真是难受
- You feeling better?  - Breaking up sucks.
-我真的好想迈克  -真遗憾
- Oh, I really miss Mike.  - Oh, I'm so sorry.
我已经试过所有疗伤法了
I've tried everything to feel better.
甚至还想要写首歌
I even tried writing a song about it...
但是我不想出任何韵律  可以配这个调的
but I can't think of anything that rhymes with:
莫妮卡  我需要你帮我渡过这段时期
Hey, Monica, I'm gonna need your help getting through this.
你不需要我帮忙吗
You're saying you're not gonna need my help?
暂不  当我准备好
No. When I get to the point where I'm ready...
要听糗死迈克笑话时
...to hear cruel, mocking jokes about Mike,
我会来找你的
I'm gonna come to you.
很好  因为我已经想出三个了
Oh, good, because I've already thought of three.
四个  我刚刚又想出第四个
Four! I just thought of a fourth!
好了  我知道我的决定是正确的
Okay. I mean, I know I did the right thing.
迈克再也不想结婚
Mike never wants to get married...
而我也不陷进一段没有未来的感情
...and I shouldn't be in a relationship that has no future.
但没多久  我就会很想他
But pretty soon, I'm gonna miss him so much...
很想再见到他
...I'm gonna want to see him again,
到时候你一定要阻止我
and you have to stop me.
好的  没问题
Okay, you got it.
除非… 我是不是太小题大做了
Unless.... Am I being too crazy about this?
好吧  就算没有未来又如何
All right, so there's no future.
那不表示我们不会快乐啊
But that doesn't mean we still can't have fun.
算了  就当我没说过
You know what? Forget what I said.
真的吗
Really?
好吧  如果你想的话
All right, if that's what you want.
那是个测试  你没及格
That was a test, and you just failed.
该死的  新手才会犯的错
Damn it! Rookie mistake!
我和恐龙做爱
I have sex with dinosaurs?
我好像有所耳闻
I believe I read that somewhere.
不只不好笑
Not only is it not funny,
而且从生理角度上这不可能  好吗
it's physically impossible! Okay?
由于物种不同
Depending on the species,
我必须要有六尺长的…
I'd have to have a 6-foot-long--
这一点儿不好笑
It's not funny!
对此我保留反对意见
I respectfully disagree.
你竟然在我的校友主页上
I can't believe you put that
写这些东西
on my alumni page.
谁在乎呢  没人会去看的
Who cares? Nobody reads those.
最好没有
You better hope not...
因为我刚刚看了你主页上发布的消息
...because I just read what you put on your page today.
我没有主页
I don't have a page.
哦  对此我保留反对意见
Oh, I respectfully disagree!
瞧瞧你  甜美天真的样子
Look at you. All sweet and innocent,
睡得像天使一样
sleeping like an angel.
被困在艾玛的肥手里
With Emma's chubby little hands wrapped around you.
没关系  艾玛  你继续睡
It's okay, Emma. You stay asleep.
不要靠近婴儿床  我有武器
Step away from the crib! I have a weapon!
没关系  瑞秋  是我
It's okay! It's okay, Rach! It's me!
快把发卷放下
Put down the scrunchie.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我听到艾玛这有声音
Well, I heard Emma stirring...
所以我过来确定一下
...so I came in to make sure
让她可以抓到哈格吉
she could reach Huggsy.
谢谢  反正醒了  我要去上厕所
Oh, thanks. All right, well, now that I'm up, I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
好的  拿去  亲爱的
Okay, there you go, sweetie.
这事没完
This isn't over!
等等  为什么罗斯要跟班里每个人说
Wait a second. Why would Ross tell everyone in your class
你始终就是个同性恋
that you are ''as gay as the day is long''?
因为我告诉大家  他跟恐龙上床
Because I told everyone he slept with dinosaurs.
那明显就是个笑话
Well, that's clearly a joke.
但是这有可能是真的
This could easily be true.
你能接一下吗
Would you get that, please?
一整天  大家不断打电话恭喜我
People have been calling to congratulate me all day.
你好
Hello?
不  他不在家  我是他老婆
No, he's not here. Yeah, this is his wife.
是啊  我也被吓了好大一跳
Yeah. Well, it came as quite a shock to me too!
嗯  我早该猜到的
Well, I guess I should've known.
他总是逼我看《红磨坊》
He just kept making me watch Moulin Rouge.
挂掉  挂掉
Hang up! Hang up!
而且那是部好电影
And that was a great movie.
我一定报复罗斯
I'm so gonna get back at Ross.
来吧  让他尝尝我的厉害  开始啦
Oh, yeah, this'll show him. Here we go.
你在做什么呢
What are you doing?
你等着看好戏吧  我的朋友
Oh, you'll see, my friend!
我死了
I'm dead?
英年早逝
And so young.
发布说我死了  这一点都不好笑
Posting that I died? That really isn't funny.
死法才比较好笑
Well, how you died was funny.
拜托  被胖子撞死
Oh, please. Hit by a blimp?
美国每年都有一个人因此丧命
It kills over one Americans every year.
难以置信  我同学们会以为我死了
Unbelievable. My classmates are gonna think I'm dead.
我的教授
My professors.
我...我的父母会接到许多电话的
My parents are gonna get phone calls!
你在玩弄大家的感请
You're messing with people's feelings here.
还跟我谈大家的感情
You wanna talk about people's feelings?
你该听听  当我告诉史登教授
You should have heard how hurt
不能跟他一起去基韦斯特度假时
Professor Stern was when I told him
他有多受伤
I wouldn't be able to go to Key West!
你玩过界了  但没关系
You've really crossed a line here. But that's okay.
因为我要去买个PS软件
Because I'm on my way to buy some Photoshop software...
和一叠的同志色情照片
...and a stack of gay porn.
没错  你的出柜将会是图文并茂
That's right. Your coming-out is about to get real graphic!
天啊  我真希望迈克在这里
God, I wish Mike were here.
好了  如果迈克在这
Okay, if Mike were here,
你们会做什么
what would the two of you be doing?
你们是动物吗  现在才下午四点
What are you, animals? It's 4:00 in the afternoon.
我给他打个电话
I gotta call him.
只是说说话  没大碍的
Just to talk to him. There's no harm in that.
开头都是这样
That's how it starts.
我不吃蛋糕  我只是要闻一下
''I don't need to eat the cake, I'll just smell the icing.
就吃一点点
Why not just a little sliver?''
或是  好吧  一两块就好
Or, ''Okay, just a slice or two.''
然后你就210磅了
The next thing you know, you're 210 pounds...
连过个通道都会被卡住
...and you get wedged in going down the tunnel slide!
菲比  亲爱的  我知道这很难
Phoebe, honey, I know this is hard.
但是如果你跟他说话
But look, if you talk to him,
你就会想见他了
then you're gonna want to see him.
如果你见了他  你就会想跟他复合了
And if you see him, you're gonna wanna get back together.
我知道  这不是你想要的
And I know that's not what you want.
好了  把电话给我
All right, so give me your phone.
给
Here.
-还有你的手机  -好吧
- And now your cell.  - Okay.
拿去
There you go.
-这是你的手机  -是啊
- This is your cell phone?  - Yes.
这是你现在用的手机
This is your current cell phone?
是的  它让我想起简单的往日
Yes. It reminds me of a simpler time.
菲比  你的包呢
Phoebe? Where's your purse?
-嘿  不行  -不
- Hey! No!  - No!
-给我  -不给你
- Give it to me!  - You can't have it!
-给我  -不要
- Give it to me!  - No!
-我会伸进去拿的  -哦  是哦
- I'll go in there!  - Oh, yeah.
-菲比  过来  -不
- Phoebe, come here!  - No!
-给我  -你疯了
- Give it to me!  - You're crazy!
去你的  莫妮卡·盖勒  宾氏
Damn you, Monica Geller hyphen Bing!
瞧瞧是谁来了
Hey, look who's here.
是乔伊带回来一个新朋友
It's Joey. And he brought home a friend.
乔伊  艾玛在这呢
Joey! Emma's right here.
你答应过白天不带女生回来
You promised not to bring girls home in the middle of the day!
不  不是女生  是…
No, no, no, it's not a girl. It's...
全新的哈格吉
...a brand-new Huggsy!
太棒了  现在艾玛有两个哈格吉了
Oh! Oh, that's so great! Now Emma has two Huggsies!
不  艾玛有一个哈格吉
No, no. Oh, no. No, Emma has one Huggsy.
新的哈格吉
The new Huggsy.
另外那个哈格吉
The other Huggsy,
我不知道  还是我把他拿回去好了
I don't know, I guess I'll just take him back.
你知道吗  小时候
You know what? When I was a little girl,
我有一只粉红色的小马叫棉花糖
I had a little pink pony named Cotton.
我非常喜欢她
Oh, I loved her so much.
去哪我都带着
I took her everywhere.
给她的尾巴编辫子
I would braid her tail--
赶紧换过来
Make the transfer!
旧哈格吉身上有个钮扣不见了
Should I be concerned that a button
我找不到
fell off the old Huggsy
不会出事吧
and I can't find it?
不  不用担心  几年前我吞下去
No, don't worry about it. I swallowed that years ago. Hey!
怎么了  我想她不喜欢新哈格吉
Oh, what? I don't think she likes the new Huggsy.
但他们是一样的啊
But he's the same.
我想她要旧的哈格吉
I think she wants the old one back.
是哦  但他们一模一样啊
Yeah, but he's the same.
乔伊  拿来
Joey, come on.
根本是一样的嘛
But he's the same!
你才不像他
You're not the same.
你这样吓不到我
You know, it's a lot less surprising to do that
别忘了是我放你上楼的
after I've buzzed you into the building.
菲比  为什么门口有男人的鞋子呢
So, Phoebe, why are there men's shoes by the door?
那是我的鞋子
Those are my shoes.
看来你复元之后  我该带你购物了
Well, when you get over this breakup, we need to go shopping.
听着  莫妮卡
Look, Monica,
我真的很感激你这样关心我
I really appreciate you checking in on me.
-我已经觉得好多了  -真的
- But I'm actually feeling a lot better.  - You are?
是  现在我想一个人待会儿
Yeah, I just kind of want to be alone right now.
-是谁  -我叫了中餐外卖
- Who's that?  - I ordered Chinese food.
真是太巧了
What are the chances?!
十亿中国人民把迈克派来了
One billion Chinese people, and they send Mike!
你来这里做什么呢
What are you doing here?
菲比打电话给我
Phoebe called me.
-菲比  -抱歉  我忍不住了
- Phoebe!  - I'm sorry. I broke down.
我想要见他
I wanted to see him.
该死的  菲比
Damn it, Phoebe,
你是怎么给他打的电话
how did you even call him?
电话主机有免提
There's a speakerphone on the base unit.
主机  用脑啊  莫妮卡  用用脑
Base unit. Think, Monica, think!
听着  如果我想见菲比  而她…
Look, if I want to see Phoebe, and she--
没你的事儿
This doesn't concern you!
抱歉  我只是听到有人提到我的名字
Sorry. I guess I was thrown off by the mention of my name.
听着  你们不能这样做
Look, guys, you can't do this.
不然分手就更难了
It's gonna make getting over each other harder.
如果我们什么都不做
Not if nothing happens.
像朋友一样相处不行吗
Why can't we just hang out as friends?
当然可以  如果你们只是朋友
Sure. If you're just gonna hang out as friends,
那我也可以加入
then maybe I'll join you.
我是你的朋友  也是迈克的朋友
You know, I'm your friend and Mike's friend.
坐下吧
Sit down.
给朋友让个位置
Make room for your friend.
你过得好不好
So how have you been?
我还挺不错的
I've been pretty good.
你真的很美
You look really beautiful.
谢谢  你看起来也不错
Thanks. You look good too.
不对  这太危险了  说话注意点
No, no, no. This is dangerous territory. Keep it clean.
钢琴弹得怎么样了
So how's the piano playing going?
我最近弹了许多情歌
Actually, I've been playing a lot of love songs lately.
-我好想你  -我也想你
- I've missed you.  - I've missed you too.
来这的路上
You know, on the way over here,
我看到一个酒鬼吐了一地
I saw this drunk guy throw up.
然后一只鸽子还去吃
And then a pigeon ate it.
嘿  罗斯
Hey. Ross.
听着  我想跟你道歉
Look, I just wanted to apologize.
别告诉我  你真的在做我的同志照
Don't tell me you actually made those gay pictures of me.
瞧瞧这个
Check this out.
原来如果我有健身  就是这样的啊
So that's what I'd look like if I worked out.
而且还是警察先生为我服务
And was being serviced by a policeman.
你不会真的发出去吧
You're not gonna actually send these out, are you?
不会了  因为你"罗斯死了" 的笑话
Actually, I don't need to, because your little ''Ross is dead'' joke
根本没效果
didn't work.
好吗  根本就没有人回应
Okay? There were no responses.
网上没人发布任何东西
Nobody posted anything on the website,
没人打电话给我父母
nobody called my parents,
该笑话你才对
so the joke is on you.
没人打电话  没人写信
Nobody called, nobody wrote anything,
没人在乎我死了
nobody cares that I'm dead.
哦  我的天啊
Oh, my God.
没有人在乎我死了吗
Nobody cares that I'm dead?
哦  别这样  你知道不是那样的
Oh, come on, you know that's not true.
说什么  你不过发布个出柜的消息
What are you talking about? You get 60 responses...
就有六十个回复
just for coming out of the closet.
我连一个回复都没有  我可是死了
I didn't get one response, and I'm dead!
嗯  同志社团比死人社团话多
Well, the gay community is a lot more vocal than the dead community.
不敢相信  连我地质学搭档都没有回复
I can't believe this. Not even my geology lab partner.
以前都是我罩他的
And I carried that guy!
我们重新想一下  好吧
Look, let's think about this, okay?
大家在这悲伤的时刻
You think people are gonna disturb your family
忍心打扰你的家人吗
at this tragic time?
有人会在网站上张贴哀悼辞吗
That people are gonna post condolences on a website?
不是说大家不在乎
This isn't about people not caring.
而是没有合适的渠道悼念
This is about people not having a decent outlet for their grief.
-说的对  的确没有合适的渠道  -没错
- You're right. There isn't a decent outlet.  - Right.
你要是办追悼会   我肯定很多人会来的
I'm sure if you had a funeral or memorial service, tons of people would come.
就是这样
Exactly!
罗斯  你要干嘛
Ross, what are you doing?
你要帮自己办追悼会
You're having a memorial service for yourself?
不  那得多傻  是你帮我办的
No, that would be stupid. You're having it for me.
罗斯  不要发出去  不要发…
Ross, don't press send. Don't press--
不  太迟了  已经发了
No, too late. Too late. It's sent.
对不起  还有你跟警察先生的照片
Sorry, so is that picture of you and the policeman.
我刚要哄艾玛睡一下
I'm trying to put Emma down for a nap.
你有看到哈格吉吗
Have you seen Huggsy?
原版的还是不好的那个
Original or crappy?
-原版的  -没有  抱歉  没有看到
- Original.  - No. Sorry. Haven't seen him.
那你床单下面那个鼓包是什么
Then what's that big lump under your covers?
是莫妮卡  行了吗
It's Monica, okay?
那才不是莫妮卡
That's not Monica!
好啦  没关系  是原版的哈格吉
All right, fine! It's original Huggsy!
我知道艾玛要他
I know Emma wants him,
但他是我的  而我需要他
but he's mine and I need him.
她真不讲理
She's being unreasonable.
乔伊  艾玛爱那个蠢企鹅是有原因的
Joey, there is a reason that Emma loves that stupid penguin so much!
别捂他耳朵
Oh, don't cover its ears!
因为这会让她想起乔伊叔叔
It's because it reminds her of her Uncle Joey.
-真的  -当然
- It does?  - Yeah.
她喜欢抱着他
And she's comforted by him
是因为她是非常爱乔伊叔叔
because she loves her Uncle Joey so much.
-真的  她爱我  -当然啦
- Really? She loves me?  - Oh, yeah.
但是你知道吗
But you know what?
如果你需要哈格吉  没关系
If you need Huggsy, don't worry.
艾玛会谅解的  我不会  但又怎样
Emma will totally understand. I won't, but whatever.
好的  等等  瑞秋  我是说如果…
Okay, wait a minute, Rach. I mean, if....
如果艾玛那么喜欢哈格吉  那么…
If Huggsy means that much to Emma, then....
嗯  就给她吧
Well, she can have him.
亲爱的  我就知道乔伊叔叔最好了
Oh, sweet, I knew Uncle Joey would step up.
瞧  艾玛  瞧瞧是谁回来了
Look, Emma. Look who's back.
不  算了  我做不到
No, forget it! Forget it! I can't do it!
你…你要把哈格吉从一个小孩手上抢走
Are you--? You're gonna take Huggsy away from a little child?
要不然你认为
How do you think
我当初怎么拿到哈格吉的
I got him in the first place?
好了  你们两个  我要去上厕所
All right, you two. I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
希望我不在的时候  不要发生什么事
I don't want anything going on while I'm gone.
有几件事你们可以讨论
Here's a few things you can discuss:
黏液  真菌  还可以想象我跟罗斯乱搞
Mucus, fungus, and the idea of me and Ross doing it.
我真的好想你
I've missed you so much.
我不会要求你复合
I won't ask you to get back together.
我知道我们要的是不同的东西 但…
I know we want different things, but....
我只想和你再多待一个晚上
Just to be with you one more night.
我也想要
I want that too.
但是那不是会让我们更痛苦吗
But is that gonna make it too hard?
还能比现在更痛苦吗
It can't be any harder than this.
如果我知道
I mean, if  had known the last time I saw you
上次是见你的最后一面  我…
would be the last time, I--
我会努力记住你的脸
I would have stopped to memorize your face,
你的一举一动
the way you moved.
你的所有
Everything about you.
如果我知道  上次是最后一次吻你…
If I had known the last time I kissed you would be the last time...
那我永远都不会停下来
I never would have stopped.
亲他  你个傻瓜
Kiss him, you fool!
-什么  -你没有听到他说什么吗
- What?  - Didn't you hear that speech?
如果你再不亲他  我就上了
If you don't kiss him, then I will.
我好想你
I missed you so much.
-我就知道你在这里  -妈的
- I knew you'd be here!  -Crap.
-他是谁  -我朋友曼尼
- Who is this?  - My friend Manny.
我请他看着我  远离你
I asked him to keep me away from you.
我也在帮菲比做同样的事
Hey, that's what I'm doing for Phoebe.
看来你做得还真差
Well, you're not doing a very good job.
-你说什么  -这个吻怎么回事
- Excuse me?  - What's with the kissing?
至少我知道我管的人在哪儿
Hey, at least I knew where my guy was.
是啊  感谢上帝
Yeah, thank God
有你在这里监看他们亲吻
you were here to oversee all the kissing.
你没有听到他说的话
You didn't hear the speech.
我听到了
I've heard the speech.
如果他知道那是最后一次…
If he knew it was gonna be the last time--
那很感人的  是你太无情了
Hey, it was very moving. You're just heartless!
-你太软弱了  -你太奇怪了
- You're weak!  -You're weird!
你裤子拉链没拉
Your pants are undone.
他们呢
Where'd they go?
-该死的  -我们搞砸了
- Damn it.  - Well, we blew it.
我只能怪我自己
I blame myself.
而我也只能怪你
And I blame you too.
已经一个小时了
It's been an hour,
我同学竟然一个都没来
and not one of my classmates has shown up?
我告诉你  要是我真的死了
I tell you, when I actually die,
有些人一定会被鬼缠死的
some people are gonna get seriously haunted.
来了  有人来了
There you go. Someone came.
好了  好了  我躲起来了
Okay. Okay. I'm gonna go hide.
太兴奋了  我第一个追悼者
This is so exciting. My first mourner!
嗨  很高兴你能够来
Hi. Glad you could come.
请进
Please come in.
你是钱德勒·宾吧
Hi. You're Chandler Bing, right?
我是汤姆·高登  是你班上的同学
I'm Tom Gordon. I was in your class.
哦  是的  是的  我来帮你拿外套
Oh, yes. Yes, let me take your coat.
谢谢  罗斯的事我很遗憾  真是…
Thanks. I'm so sorry about Ross, it's....
没关系  至少他去世时正在做喜欢的事
No, at least he died doing what he loved.
看大胖子
Watching blimps.
那是谁
Who is it?
你认识一个叫汤姆·高登的吗
You know some guy, Tom Gordon?
我不记得他了
I don't remember him.
但是  我启发过太多人了
But then again, I touched so many lives.
那你跟罗斯很熟吗
So did you know Ross well?
不算认识
Actually, I barely knew him.
我来是因为听到钱德勒的事
I came because I heard Chandler's news.
他有对象了吗
Do you know if he's seeing anyone?
是的  他有  就是我
Yes, he is. Me.
什么  你是说…
What? You mean--?
我可以问你一个私人问题吗
Can I ask you a personal question?
你是怎么把胡子刮得这么干净的
How do you shave your beard so close?
好了  小汤姆  你哀悼得够了
Okay, Tommy! That's enough mourning for you.
走吧  再见  好了
Here we go. Bye-bye. All right.
-听着  打电话给我  -好的
- Hey, listen. Call me.  - Okay.
没人关心我的死活吗
I'm dead and no one cares?
我看起来像男人吗
I look like a man?
拜托  荒谬的问题  一次一个就好
Please, one ridiculous problem at a time.
这并不荒谬  你看嘛  根本没有人来
This isn't ridiculous. Look around, no one's here.
你只给他们一天的时间
You gave them one day's notice.
又不是每个人天天都上网
Not everyone checks the website every day.
而有莫妮卡  或许因为你的站像
And Monica, it's probably the way you stand!
你说的可能对
I guess you're right.
但是  总该要有人看到啊
Still, somebody must have seen it.
我在学校上了四年
I went to that school for four years
竟然没有影响到任何人
and I didn't have an impact on anyone?
嗯  不是那样的  你有影响到我啊
Well, that's not true. You had an impact on me.
已经十五年了
I mean, it's 15 years later
我们依旧是最要好的朋友
and we're still best friends.
对你来说  这不算什么吗
Doesn't that count for something?
太好了  更多狂野男孩来找钱德勒了
Oh, great, more party boys for Chandler.
我敢说一定是来看你的  去躲起来
I'm sure it's somebody for you. Now go hide.
嗨  我来参加罗斯·盖勒的追悼会
Hi. I'm here for Ross Geller's memorial service.
-可芮  可芮·薇丝顿  -是的
- Kori? Kori Weston?  - Yeah.
-你可真漂亮  -你是谁呢
- You look amazing.  - And you are?
钱德勒  钱德勒·宾
Chandler. Chandler Bing.
而且我不是同志  我一点都不是
And I'm not gay. I'm not gay at all.
但你是已婚的
You are married, though.
别听这哥们的  他只是心情很差
Don't listen to him. He's in a really bad mood.
我不敢相信罗斯去世了  太难过了
I can't believe that Ross is gone. It is just so sad.
我不知道罗斯跟你很熟
I didn't know Ross and you were so close.
并没有  但我们一起上过课  他
Oh, we weren't. But we had one class together.
是个很棒的人
He was such a great guy.
每次谈到科学都激情四射
And he talked so passionately about science.
我一直记得他
I always remembered him.
我肯定这话对他很重要
I'm sure that would mean a lot to him.
而且如果天堂有一扇门
And if heaven has a door...
我敢说  他一定耳朵贴着门专心在听
...I'm sure he's pressing his ear up against it and listening intently.
我好多次都想打电话约他出去
I thought so many times about calling him and asking him out.
大概我再也没有机会了
I guess I really missed my chance.
不  你还有机会
No, you didn't!
我还活着
I'm still alive!
可芮  我知道你很惊讶
Kori, I know this is a big surprise for you.
说来话长
It's a long story.
但是你刚说的话
But the things you just said
让我这一天变得很美好
really made my day.
你能来  对我意义重大
The fact that you're here means more to me...
比房间都挤满了人还要好
...than if this room were filled with people.
你这变态  谁会做这种事
You sick freak! Who does that?
不敢相信我还喜欢过你
I can't believe I had a crush on you.
你们有听到吗
Did you hear that?
可芮·薇丝顿喜欢过我
Kori Weston had a crush on me!
没啦  妈  我没死
No, Mom, I am not dead.
我知道这种事情不能开玩笑
I know it's not something to kid about.
只是我跟钱德勒之间的恶作剧
It was just a practical joke between Chandler and me,
已经结束了  好吗
but it's over, okay?
不会的  即使我死了
Actually, no. Even if I had died,
你也不会后继无人的
you would not be left childless.
莫妮卡
Monica?